JOE：Hello, sit anywhere you like.
JOE：いらっしゃい。お好きなところにどうぞ。
Young Man：Do you have saké?
少年：日本酒はありますか？
JOE：Yep, wait one sec.
JOE：日本酒ね。
JOE：Do you want it heated?
JOE：温める？
Young Man：No.
少年：いえ。
JOE：Never seen you before. Are you from the east? Node 03?
JOE：お客さん、見たことない顔だね。 東方の人？Node03出身？
Young Man：Yes. Is it rare to see one around these places?
少年：はい、ここにはあまりいないんですか？
JOE：Nah, where do you think this is? It's 08, any type of people can be found here.
JOE：まさか。Node08にはどんな人間だっているよ。
JOE：But cold saké... indeed not an order you see every day.
JOE：でも、冷たい日本酒を頼む人は珍しいね。
Young Man：Back home we call this "Yukihie", refreshes the brain quite well... *Gulp!*
少年：僕の故郷では、「雪冷え」って言います。飲むと頭がシャキッとするんですよ。ゴクッ
JOE："Yukihie", I see...
JOE：「雪冷え」…か……
Young Man：*Gulp!*
少年：ゴクッ
JOE：Jasus, slow down. If you get drunk so fast, I'm gonna be the one carrying your limp body outside.
JOE：ちょっと、お客さんペース速すぎ！酔っぱらっちゃったら、追い出さないといけなくなっちゃうから。
JOE：I've always had a fond interest in chatting with customers from other Nodes.
JOE：俺、他のNodeの人と話すの好きなんだよ。
Young Man：I'm... not exactly the type who's good at chatting.
少年：僕は…話すのとか得意じゃないです。
JOE：Haha, it's fine.
JOE：ハハハ！大丈夫だって！
JOE：I'm JOE, and you are?
JOE：俺はJOE、君は？
Young Man：Hayato... *Gulp!*
少年：隼人……ゴク
JOE：Did you get dumped?
JOE：何？失恋？
Hayato：……... Why did you ask?
Hayato：……なんでですか？
JOE：Well, a young fella with a depressed look visiting an unfamiliar bar with the sole purpose of getting trashed.
JOE：夜中に一人で、入ったことのないバーで、浴びるように酒を飲む若者なんて
JOE：Pretty sure that means it has something to do with relationship issues... I think?
JOE：0％落ち込んだ人間だよ。……タブン。
Hayato：I'm... looking for a female.
Hayato：女の人を……探してるんです。
JOE：Girlfriend?
JOE：彼女？
Hayato：More or less my childhood friend, been missing for years already... *Gulp!*
Hayato：幼なじみで、もう何年も前に行方不明になっちゃったんですけど……ゴクッ
JOE：For years... could it be that she already... ah, I'm sorry.
JOE：何年も前……それじゃ、もしかすると……あっ、ご、ごめん。
Hayato：No need to be...I gave up a long time ago too.
Hayato：いえ…僕も半ば諦めかけてたんです。
Hayato：In Node 03, missing people usually stay missing forever. It's practically a part of everyday life.
Hayato：Node03では、人が消えて二度と帰って来ないなんて日常茶飯事ですから。
Hayato：However, for some unknown reason, I just always have this feeling that she is right here in Node 08. A very powerful feeling too...*Gulp!*
Hayato：でも、なんか、彼女はNode08にいるような気がして。 それもなぜだか強烈にそう感じるんです……ゴクッ
JOE：... If you're looking for someone, maybe you've come to the right location.
JOE：……人探しなら、ここに来たのは正解かもね。
JOE：Not to brag about it, but this little shop really has all kinds of people visiting every day.
JOE：自慢じゃないけど、ここには本当にどんな人間でもいるから。
JOE：Give me some hints, maybe I can help. If you have a photo, even better.
JOE：手掛かりさえあれば、手伝えるかもしれない。 写真とかないの？
Hayato：A photo... I always have it with me. Here.
Hayato：写真……ずっと持ち歩いてます。 これ……
JOE：Hoho, lemme take a look. Heard from folks that Node 03 is where all the cute gals are at...
JOE：お、どれどれ。 いやぁ、Node03は美女ばかりって聞くからなぁ……
JOE：……！
JOE：……！
JOE：...... This person......
JOE：……この子は……